Office of Corporate and Foundation Relations Records UA199
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Corporate and Foundation Relations Records
1954 -- 2008
1980 -- 2000
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Corporate and Foundation Relations
University Advancement Division
UA199
33.6 Linear Feet 28 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Corporate prospect files and Foundation prospect files.
Biographical / Historical
The Corporate and Foundation Relations (CFR) team at Tufts University is the starting point for organizations wishing to develop unique and profitable partnerships with a world-class teaching and research institution.
CFR is part of University Advancement.
Conditions Governing Access
Records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
Scope and Contents
These records demonstrate the relationship between CFR and various corporate and foundation funding sources for the promotion of grants and activities at Tufts University. Some records contain legacy correspondence that pre-dates the existence of the Office of CFR. Materials include correspondence, memos, clippings, company and foundation reports, grant reports, and financial information. The bulk of the records date from the 1980s and 1990s.
Advancement
- Foundation Prospect Files, 1959 -- 2008; 1980 -- 2000; UA199.002; 19.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  These records document the relationship between CFR and various foundation funding sources for the promotion of grants and activities at Tufts University. File contain correspondence, agreements, research materials, and promotional materials.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by accession.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - AFAR Foundation [1 of 2], 1994 -- 2003; UA199.002.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - AFAR Foundation [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; UA199.002.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Medical Research Foundation, 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Alden Trust, 1988 -- 2001; UA199.002.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Allen Foundation, 1996 -- 1998; UA199.002.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - American Astronomical Society, 2001; UA199.002.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - AmFAR (American Foundation for AIDS Research) [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1995; UA199.002.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - AmFAR (American Foundation for AIDS Research) [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1989; UA199.002.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - American Fund for Dental Health, 1991 -- 1993; UA199.002.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - American International Group, 2000; UA199.002.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Annenberg CPB#2 1993-present [1 of 2], 1993 -- 2005; UA199.002.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Annenberg CPB#2 1993-present [2 of 2], 1993 -- 2005; UA199.002.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - ARA Paresghian Medical Research Foundation, 1999 -- 2000; UA199.002.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Art Matters, Incorporated, 1990; UA199.002.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Asia Foundation, 2000; UA199.002.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1987; UA199.002.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Associated Grantmakers of Massachusetts, Inc., 1995; UA199.002.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Atlas Family Foundation, 1999; UA199.002.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - "B" Misc., 2003 -- 2007; UA199.002.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Balfour Foundation, 1983 -- 1992; UA199.002.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Balfour Foundation #2 [1 of 2], 1994 -- 2001; UA199.002.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Balfour Foundation #2 [2 of 2], 1994 -- 2001; UA199.002.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Banbury Fund, 2001; UA199.002.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Banyan Tree Foundation, 1997 -- 1998; UA199.002.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - Barbour Foundation, Beatrice, 1990 -- 2000; UA199.002.013.00025 (Box 13)
  - Bayne Fund, Howard, 2001; UA199.002.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - Bay Foundation, 1978 -- 2002; UA199.002.013.00027 (Box 13)
  - Bechtel, Jr. (S.D.) Foundation, 1990; UA199.002.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - Beidler Charitable Trust, Francis, 1993 -- 1997; UA199.002.013.00029 (Box 13)
  - Beinecke Foundation, Inc., 1998; UA199.002.013.00030 (Box 13)
  - Blum Foundation, Edith C., 1998; UA199.002.013.00031 (Box 13)
  - Bodman Foundation, 1987; UA199.002.013.00032 (Box 13)
  - Bobst Foundation, Elmer and Mamdouha, 1998; UA199.002.013.00033 (Box 13)
  - Bonner Foundation, Corella and Bertram, 1996; UA199.002.013.00034 (Box 13)
  - Bosch Foundation, Robert, 1983 -- 1986; UA199.002.013.00035 (Box 13)
  - Boston Women's Fund, 1992; UA199.002.013.00036 (Box 13)
  - Bostwick Foundation, Albert C., 2001; UA199.002.013.00037 (Box 13)
  - Bradshaw Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.013.00038 (Box 13)
  - Breidenthal-Snyder Foundation, 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.013.00039 (Box 13)
  - Brodsky Family Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.013.00040 (Box 13)
  - Brookdale Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.013.00041 (Box 13)
  - Brooks Foundation, Gladys, 1983 -- 2000; UA199.002.013.00042 (Box 13)
  - Buck Institute for Education, 2001; UA199.002.013.00043 (Box 13)
  - Burroughs Welcome Fund, 1991 -- 2008; UA199.002.013.00044 (Box 13)
  - "C" Misc., 2003 -- 2007; UA199.002.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Calder Foundation, Louis, 1985 -- 1996; UA199.002.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - California Wellness Foundation, 1995; UA199.002.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - CAP CURE Foundation [1 of 2], 1995 -- 1998; UA199.002.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - CAP CURE Foundation [2 of 2], 1996; UA199.002.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Carlisle Foundation (1991-Present), 1990 -- 1999; UA199.002.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Carnegie Corporation [1 of 2], 1996; UA199.002.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Carnegie Corporation [2 of 2], 1993 -- 1996; UA199.002.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Carthage Foundation, 1987 -- 1995; UA199.002.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Casey Foundation, Annie, 1993 -- 1996; UA199.002.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Castle Rock Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Cedar Tree Foundation, 2003; UA199.002.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Center for Global Partnership, 2003; UA199.002.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Chase Foundation, Alfred E., 1996 -- 1997; UA199.002.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Chen, Francis, 2001 -- 2005; UA199.002.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Child Health Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Children's Research and Education Institute (CREI), 1989; UA199.002.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Children Now Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Christensen Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Claiborne (Liz) and Art Ortenberg Foundation, 1997; UA199.002.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Commonwealth Fund (1987-present) [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1999; UA199.002.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Commonwealth Fund (1987-present) [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1995; UA199.002.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Concern Foundation [1 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA199.002.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Concern Foundation [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1996; UA199.002.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Condakes Charitable Foundation, Leo and Eve, 2001; UA199.002.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Connelly Foundation, 1994; UA199.002.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Cosby Foundation, Ennis and William (Hello Friend), 1997 -- 1999; UA199.002.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Council for Biotechnology Information, 2001; UA199.002.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Cow Hollow Foundation, 1999; UA199.002.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Cox Foundation, James M., 1999; UA199.002.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Crossroads Community Foundation, 2000 -- 2001; UA199.002.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Culpepper, Charles E. (1988-Present) [1 of 2], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Culpepper, Charles E. (1988-Present) [2 of 2], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Cultural Initiative Foundation, 1995 -- 1997; UA199.002.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Cummings Foundation, Nathan [1 of 3], 2002 -- 2007; UA199.002.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Cummings Foundation, Nathan [2 of 3], 1990 -- 1999; UA199.002.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Cummings Foundation, Nathan [3 of 3], 1988 -- 1990; UA199.002.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Cystic Fibrosis Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - "D" Misc., 2003 -- 2008; UA199.002.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - DR Fund, 2000; UA199.002.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Dana Foundation, Charles #2 (1986-present), 1986 -- 1997; UA199.002.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Dana Foundation, Eleanor Taylor, 1987 -- 1991; UA199.002.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Danforth Foundation [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1997; UA199.002.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Danforth Foundation [2 of 2], 1979 -- 1988; UA199.002.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Dangberg Foundation, Inc., Grace, 1988; UA199.002.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Davenport Family Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - DeCamp Foundation, Ira W., 1991 -- 2002; UA199.002.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Deer Creek Foundation, 1988 -- 1998; UA199.002.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Delany Trust, 1991 -- 1998; UA199.002.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Dewar Foundation, 1990 -- 2001; UA199.002.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Dodge Foundation, Cleveland H., 1988; UA199.002.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Dodge Foundation, Geraldine Rockefeller [1 of 2], 1978 -- 2001; UA199.002.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Dodge Foundation, Geraldine Rockefeller [2 of 2], 1982 -- 1990; UA199.002.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Donner Foundation, 1989 -- 2003; UA199.002.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Dorot Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Dupont Foundation Inc., Chichester, 2001; UA199.002.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Dusky Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Educational Foundation of America, 1987 -- 1999; UA199.002.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Educational Foundation of America (File #2), 1991 -- 1998; UA199.002.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Ellsworth Foundation, Ruth and Warren A., 2003; UA199.002.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Emma Foundation (Queen), 1993; UA199.002.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Energy Foundation, 1991 -- 1995; UA199.002.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Englehard Foundation, Charles, 1997; UA199.002.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, 2001; UA199.002.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Erpf Fund, Armand G., 1979 -- 1985; UA199.002.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - Esselstyn Foundation, 1993; UA199.002.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - Eurasia Foundation, 1996; UA199.002.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Exxon Education Foundation (1985-present), 1984 -- 1999; UA199.002.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - "F" Misc., 2004 -- 2007; UA199.002.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - Fairchild Foundation, 1982 -- 1998; UA199.002.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - Farm Foundation, 1996; UA199.002.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Farnsworth Trust, 1982 -- 2003; UA199.002.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Feldberg Family Foundation, 1982; UA199.002.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Feldman Family Foundation, 1986; UA199.002.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Filene Foundation, 1982 -- 1994; UA199.002.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Fishbein Family IC Research Foundation, 1999; UA199.002.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Fisher Armed Services (Zachary and Elizabeth), 1995; UA199.002.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Food for All, 1996; UA199.002.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation [1 of 4], 2001 -- 2002; UA199.002.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation [2 of 4], 2000 -- 2001; UA199.002.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation [3 of 4], 1999 -- 2001; UA199.002.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation [4 of 4], 1998 -- 1999; UA199.002.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation (1995-1997) [1 of 2], UA199.002.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation (1995-1997) [2 of 2], UA199.002.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Ford Foundation, Edward E., 1996; UA199.002.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Forsyth Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Foundation for Children with Learning Disabilities, 1981 -- 1982; UA199.002.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Foundation for Deep Ecology, 1996 -- 2000; UA199.002.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Foundation for the Future, 1998; UA199.002.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Foundation for Independent Higher Education, 1997; UA199.002.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Foundation for Middle East [Peace], 1984 -- 1986; UA199.002.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Freedom Fund (formerly Gannett), 1982 -- 1991; UA199.002.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Frueauff Foundation, 1985 -- 1998; UA199.002.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Fry Foundation, Lloyd A., 1986 -- 1998; UA199.002.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Future Generations Alliance, 1995; UA199.002.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - "G" Misc., 2003 -- 2008; UA199.002.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - Gaulin Foundation, Andree and Jean, 2002 -- 2003; UA199.002.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Gauntlett Foundation, Barbara, 1994; UA199.002.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - German Marshall Fund, 1982 -- 1994; UA199.002.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Gerondelis Foundation Inc., 1985 -- 1998; UA199.002.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Getty Trust, J.P., 1985 -- 2000; UA199.002.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Gilman Foundation, Howard [1 of 3], 1994 -- 1998; UA199.002.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - Gilman Foundation, Howard [2 of 3], 1993 -- 1995; UA199.002.016.00033 (Box 16)
  - Gilman Foundation, Howard [3 of 3], 1992 -- 1993; UA199.002.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - Global Alliance for Workers and Communities, 2002 -- 2003; UA199.002.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Goldman Foundation, Herman, 2002 -- 2003; UA199.002.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Goode Trust, Edith, 1996 -- 1997; UA199.002.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Goodwin, Neva Friends, 2001; UA199.002.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Gordon Fund, 1998; UA199.002.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Gorin Foundation, Nehemias, 1986 -- 1989; UA199.002.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Grand Circle Foundation Inc., 1998; UA199.002.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Grant Foundation, W.T. [1 of 5], 2002; UA199.002.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Grant Foundation, W.T. [2 of 5], 2001; UA199.002.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Grant Foundation, W.T. [3 of 5], 1991 -- 2000; UA199.002.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Grant Foundation, W.T. [4 of 5], 1982 -- 1990; UA199.002.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Grant Foundation, W.T. [5 of 5], 1989 -- 1997; UA199.002.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Grausz, Henry, 1994; UA199.002.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Gravity Research Foundation, 1986 -- 2005; UA199.002.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Greater Boston Council on Alcoholism, 1999; UA199.002.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Greenwall Foundation, 1991 -- 1997; UA199.002.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - Greve Foundation, William and Mary, 1981 -- 1990; UA199.002.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - GTE Foundation Gift Program [1 of 2], 1995; UA199.002.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - GTE Foundation Gift Program [2 of 2], 1994; UA199.002.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - GTE Correspondence [1 of 2], 1979 -- 1994; UA199.002.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - GTE Correspondence [2 of 2], 1979 -- 1994; UA199.002.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, Harry Frank, 1995; UA199.002.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, John Simon, 2001; UA199.002.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - "H" Misc., 2006 -- 2007; UA199.002.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Hague Appeal for Peace, 2000; UA199.002.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Hallowell Chair, 1982 -- 1991; UA199.002.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Harrington Foundation, Francis A. and Jacueline, 2000; UA199.002.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Hasbro Children's Foundation, 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Hassenfeld, 1982; UA199.002.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Hauser Foundation, 1999; UA199.002.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Hayden Foundation (1988-Present), 1988 -- 1998; UA199.002.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - Haymarket Peoples Fund, 2002; UA199.002.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Health Effects Institute, 1986; UA199.002.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - Heinz Family Foundation, 1998 -- 2001; UA199.002.017.00034 (Box 17)
  - Heinz Endowments, Howard and Vira, 1998; UA199.002.017.00035 (Box 17)
  - Hewlett Mellon Challenge Grant, 1986 -- 1992; UA199.002.017.00036 (Box 17)
  - Hewlett Foundation, William and Flora [1 of 2], 1988 -- 2002; UA199.002.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Hewlett Foundation, William and Flora [2 of 2], 1988 -- 2002; UA199.002.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Higgins Foundation, Aldus, 1982; UA199.002.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - High Meadow Foundation, 1990; UA199.002.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Hood Foundation, Charles H. [1 of 2], 1977 -- 1998; UA199.002.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Hood Foundation, Charles H. [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; UA199.002.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Host Foundation, 1985 -- 1994; UA199.002.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Hostetter Foundation, Amos, 1998; UA199.002.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Howard Foundation, 1992 -- 1999; UA199.002.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute [1 of 3], 1975 -- 2002; UA199.002.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute [2 of 3], 1996 -- 2002; UA199.002.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute [3 of 3], 1995 -- 1998; UA199.002.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Hurdle Hill, 1992; UA199.002.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - Hyams Foundation, 2000 -- 2001; UA199.002.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - "I" Misc., 2007; UA199.002.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Indiana Historical Society, 1993; UA199.002.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Infinity Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - International Foundation, 1992 -- 1995; UA199.002.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - International Human Relations Institute, 1991; UA199.002.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - International Life Sciences Institute (ILSI), 1996 -- 1999; UA199.002.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - International Nutrition Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - International Research and Exchange (IREX), 1995; UA199.002.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - Irving, J.D. Forest Forest Advisory Council, 1999 -- 2001; UA199.002.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Ischemia Research and Education, 2002; UA199.002.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Island Foundation, 1993 -- 1995; UA199.002.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Ittleson Foundation Inc., 1981 -- 2002; UA199.002.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - "J" Misc., 2001 -- 2002; UA199.002.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - J.M. Foundation, 1986 -- 1989; UA199.002.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - JSM Charitable Trust, 1997; UA199.002.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Jacobs Foundation, Johann, 1999 -- 2000; UA199.002.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Japan Forum, 1995 -- 2003; UA199.002.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - Johnson Foundation [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Johnson Foundation [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1989; UA199.002.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - Johnson Endeavor Foundation, Christian A., 1982 -- 1994; UA199.002.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood [1 of 6], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood [2 of 6], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood [3 of 6], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood [4 of 6], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Johnson, Robert Woof [5 of 6], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood [6 of 6], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Jones Foundation, W. Alton [2 of 2], 1980 -- 1998; UA199.002.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Jones Foundation, W. Alton [1 of 2], 1980 -- 1998; UA199.002.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Joyce Foundation [1 of 2], 1980 -- 2000; UA199.002.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Joyce Foundation [2 of 2], 1980 -- 2000; UA199.002.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation International, 1999; UA199.002.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - "K" misc, 2002 -- 2007; UA199.002.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Kaiser Foundation, Henry J [1 of 4], 1988 -- 2008; UA199.002.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Kaiser Foundation, Henry J [2 of 4], 1988 -- 2008; UA199.002.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Kaiser Foundation, Henry J [3 of 4], 1988 -- 2008; UA199.002.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Kaiser Foundation, Henry J [4 of 4], 1988 -- 2008; UA199.002.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Kapor Family Foundation, 1989; UA199.002.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Kapor Foundation, Mitchel, 2002; UA199.002.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Karamanlis Chair, 2000; UA199.002.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Kaufman Foundation [1 of 2], 1992 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Kaufman Foundation [2 of 2], 1992 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [1 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [2 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [3 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [4 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [5 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [6 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [7 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [8 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [9 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Keck Foundation [10 of 10], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1994; UA199.002.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg Foundation [1 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; UA199.002.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg Foundation [2 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; UA199.002.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg Foundation [1 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA199.002.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg Foundation [2 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA199.002.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1998 -- 1999; UA199.002.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Kennedy Foundation, Joseph P., 1982 -- 1998; UA199.002.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Kettering Foundation, Charles F. [1 of 2], 1979 -- 1988; UA199.002.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Kettering Foundation, Charles F. [2 of 2], 1995 -- 2001; UA199.002.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Kettering Family Foundation, 1981; UA199.002.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Kleberg Foundation, 1981 -- 1999; UA199.002.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Klingenstein Fund, 1994; UA199.002.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - Knapp Foundation, 1981 -- 1999; UA199.002.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - Knight Foundation, 1987 -- 1998; UA199.002.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Korea Foundation, 1994 -- 1997; UA199.002.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - Kresge Foundation Challenge Athletic Fieldhouse, 1996 -- 1998; UA199.002.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Kresge Library Proposal, 1992 -- 1994; UA199.002.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - Kresge Equipment Fund [1 of 3], 1992 -- 1997; UA199.002.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - Kresge Equipment Fund [2 of 3], 1989 -- 1991; UA199.002.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - Kresge Equipment Fund [3 of 3], 1990 -- 1991; UA199.002.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - Kress Foundation, 1983 -- 1999; UA199.002.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - Kuwait-America Foundation, 1995; UA199.002.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - "L" Misc., 1999 -- 2008; UA199.002.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - Larsen Fund, 2001; UA199.002.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - Lauder Foundation, Estee, 1985 -- 1992; UA199.002.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Leir, Henry, 1993; UA199.002.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - Lily Endowment, Inc., 1988 -- 2000; UA199.002.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - Link Foundation, 2001 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - List Foundation, Inc., Albert A., 1998; UA199.002.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - Loundsbery Foundation, Richard, 1989 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - Luce Foundation, Henry [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.021.00010 (Box 21)
  - Luce Foundation, Henry [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - Luce Foundation, Clare Booth-Luce Program [1 of 2], 1994 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - Luce Foundation, Clare Booth-Luce Program [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1994; UA199.002.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - Luce Professorship in Science and Humanitarianism, 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - Luce Professorship in Science and Humanitarianism [2], 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00015 (Box 21)
  - Luce Foundation, Henry #1, 1995 -- 1998; UA199.002.021.00016 (Box 21)
  - Luce Foundation, Henry #2, 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - Lufkin Trust, 2000 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00018 (Box 21)
  - Lufkin Trust [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1999; UA199.002.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - Lufkin Trust [2 of 2], 1993 -- 1999; UA199.002.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - Lufkin Trust [1 of 2], 1959 -- 1992; UA199.002.021.00021 (Box 21)
  - Lufkin Trust [2 of 2], 1959 -- 1992; UA199.002.021.00022 (Box 21)
  - "M" Misc., 1997 -- 2008; UA199.002.021.00023 (Box 21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, J Roderick, 1989; UA199.002.021.00024 (Box 21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, John D. and Catherine T. [1 of 3], 1993 -- 1998; UA199.002.021.00025 (Box 21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, John D. and Catherine T. [2 of 3], 1993 -- 1998; UA199.002.021.00026 (Box 21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, John D. and Catherine T. [3 of 3], 1993 -- 1998; UA199.002.021.00027 (Box 21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, John D. and Catherine T., 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.021.00028 (Box 21)
  - MacMillan Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.022.00001 (Box 22)